$ApocalypseSpells	Apocalypse Spells
$General_Page	General
$AlterationBalance_Header	Alteration Balance
$ThrummingStone	Thrumming Stone
$ThrummingStoneAlterationBalance_Help	The rate at which the Thrumming Stone spell emits its shockwave pulses.
$ConjurationBalance_Header	Conjuration Balance
$AvengingWraith	Avenging Wraith
$AvengingWraithConjurationBalance_Help	The percentage of the killer's stats inherited by the next Avenging Wraith summoned. Should an Avenging Wraith die of natural causes, it defaults to 50 Health, Magicka and Stamina.
$DremoraAssassin	Dremora Assassin
$DremoraAssassinConjurationBalance_Help	A Dremora Assassin will curse targets below this amount of Health with Death Mark, temporarily reducing their Health to 1.
$Lich	Lich
$LichConjurationBalance_Help	The amount of weapon charge required to summon a Lich.
$IllusionBalance_Header	Illusion Balance
$HarrowingDirge	Harrowing Dirge
$HarrowingDirgeIllusionBalance_Help	The amount of damage dealt by Harrowing Dirge as a percentage of each target's maximum Health when a target dies.
$RestorationBalance_Header	Restoration Balance
$Bloodseeker	Bloodseeker
$BloodseekerRestorationBalance_Help	The percentage of Health the target has lost or gained while Bloodseeker is in flight that is applied as damage or healing when it hits the target.
$FingerofDeath	Finger of Death
$FingerofDeathRestorationBalance_Help	The percentage of a target's Health dealt as damage to the caster of Finger of Death.
$WellingBlood	Welling Blood
$WellingBloodRestorationBalance_Help	The amount of Health the target must lose during the course of a Welling Blood spell to trigger the instant death effect.
$KingsHeartImprovesCraftingSkills	King's Heart Improves Crafting Skills
$KingsHeartImprovesCraftingSkillsRestorationBalance_Help	By default, the King's Heart spell improves all skills except crafting skills. Use this option to allow it to improve crafting skills as well.
$Features_Header	Features
$MindControlSpellscanaffectAnyTarget	Mind Control Spells can affect Any Target
$MindControlSpellscanaffectAnyTargetFeatures_Help	Allows spells that control other actors (Mind Control, Mirror Entity) to affect targets of any race. Non-humanoid races may randomly become invisible or immobile or fail to attack. But if you want to try it anyway, enable this option.
$ExperienceGainModifiers_Header	Experience Gain Modifiers
$ScriptedExperienceGain	Scripted Experience Gain
$ScriptedExperienceGainExperienceGainModifiers_Help	Multiplier for the experience granted by spells with variable experience rewards (for instance, instant death spells that grant experience based on the remaining Health of the target). These experience rewards are not affected by mods that change experience gain. This setting also affects the spells below.
$AtronachMark	Atronach Mark
$AtronachMarkExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Atronach Mark spell per point of damage dealt.
$BloodseekerExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Bloodseeker spell per point of damage or healing.
$EmpathicAgony	Empathic Agony
$EmpathicAgonyExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Empathic Agony spell per point of damage dealt.
$HarrowingDirgeExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Harrowing Dirge spell per point of damage dealt.
$MagickaVoid	Magicka Void
$MagickaVoidExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Magicka Void spell per point of damage dealt.
$MimicsCloak	Mimic's Cloak
$MimicsCloakExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Mimic's Cloak spell per spell copied.
$ScreamofPain	Scream of Pain
$ScreamofPainExperienceGainModifiers_Help	The amount of experience granted by the Scream of Pain spell per point of temporary Health loss.
$Troubleshooting_Header	Troubleshooting
$RepopulateLeveledLists	Repopulate Leveled Lists
$RepopulateLeveledListsTroubleshooting_Help	This option first cleans up spell vendor inventories and drop lists by removing all Apocalypse tomes, scrolls and staves, then repopulates those lists with the latest Apocalypse items. Use this option when upgrading from an older version of Apocalypse and certain spells are missing.\nThis will not affect other mods that modify leveled lists UNLESS they do so through scripting, in which case it will remove those changes. Please note that spell vendors require 48 hours to restock.
$SpawnBackupVendor	Spawn Backup Vendor
$SpawnBackupVendorTroubleshooting_Help	Apocalypse features scripting to dynamically populate the inventories of spell vendors and drop lists. If this script fails for any reason, use this option to spawn a backup vendor at the Lady Stone. Kyrgar the Hidden sells all spells you meet the skill level requirements for. This could be considered cheating and is immersion breaking, so this option is disabled by default.
$Maintenance_Page	Maintenance
$AutoloadSettings_Header	Autoload Settings
$Enabled	Enabled
$EnabledMaintenance_Help	Uncheck this option if you want mod-specific variables not to be loaded. This does not apply to variables in the settings file and when the script is upgraded to a newer version. Disabling this option is useful when there are conflicts with other mods during autoload.
$LoadingDelay	Loading Delay
$LoadingDelayMaintenance_Help	Settings loading delay in seconds. Useful if the mod takes time to initialize.
$LoadSettings	Load Settings
$LoadSettingsMaintenance_Help	Forces the modification to reload the settings. Useful if autoloading is disabled.
$ResetSettings	Reset Settings
$ResetSettingsMaintenance_Help	Reset settings to default values.
$LoadSettingsonReload	Load Settings on Reload
$LoadSettingsonReloadMaintenance_Help	Check this option if you want the settings to be loaded every time you load the game. Useful if you have something that reverts settings. This option will not work if the base mod does not use the OnGameReload event or if you disabled Autoload.
$Verbose	Verbose
$VerboseMaintenance_Help	Check this option to see additional information during loader work.
